<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1250"?>
<document>
    <update name="2023.02.19" id="20230219" time="19.02.2023">
        <li>Fix 'download failed' error (caused by website workflow change)</li>
        <li>Fix crashes on Systems running Android 7 or below when statusbar icon is activated</li>
        <li>Change: 'acquire map from c:geo' removed due to map incompatibilities</li>
    </update>
    <update name="2022.01.14" id="20220114" time="14.01.2022">
        <li>Fix Android 12 GPS problem</li>
        <li>Restore functionality of OSM Mapnik online map</li>
        <li>New app icon and minor style adjustments</li>                   
        <li>Modernize app settings screens</li>
        <li>Validation of login credentials in settings</li>
        <li>Various translation updates</li>
        <li>Some small code optimizations and bug fixes</li>
        <li>Compile with a new target version to fulfill Google requirements - Please report any new issues to our support</li>
        <li>Fix: Crash on change of some global settings</li>
        <li>Fix: No app icon in status bar notification</li>
        <li>Minimum required Android version is now 5.0. A legacy version is available for Android 4.1 up to 4.4.</li>
    </update>
    <update name="2020.08.21" id="20200821" time="21.08.2020">
        <li>Get link to offline maps from c:geo in map menu. Note: Requires Mapsforge V3 map in c:geo as WhereYouGo still only supports this version.</li>                   
        <li>Various translation updates</li>                   
        <li>New launcher icon according to Google Play requirements</li>
        <li>Improve login usability by providing error messages in case of missing or wrong credentials</li>
        <li>Make screen rotation optional</li>
        <li>Use new whereyougo@cgeo.org support mail</li>
        <li>Adjust map font size for devices with higher DPI</li>
        <li>New option for automatic text scaling on maps</li>
        <li>Optimize caching of map tiles and adjust menu entries for it</li>
        <li>Android 8 fix for getting GPS when running in background</li>
    </update>
</document>
