<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1250"?>
<document>
    <update name="2020.08.20" id="20200820" time="20.08.2020">
        <li>Get link to offline maps from c:geo in map menu. Note: Requires Mapsforge V3 map in c:geo as WhereYouGo still only supports this version.</li>                   
        <li>Various translation updates</li>                   
        <li>New launcher icon according to Google Play requirements</li>
        <li>Improve login usability by providing error messages in case of missing or wronfg credentials</li>
        <li>Make screen rotation optional</li>
        <li>Use new whereyougo@cgeo.org support mail</li>
        <li>Adjust map font size for devices with higher DPI</li>
        <li>New option for automatic text scaling on maps</li>
        <li>Optimize caching of map tiles and adjust menu entries for it</li>
        <li>Android 8 fix for getting GPS when running in background</li>
    </update>
    <update name="2020.04.07" id="20200407" time="07.04.2020">
        <li>Fix crash on starting cartridge on Android 8 devices</li>                   
        <li>Allow the app to run in landscape mode</li>                   
        <li>Update translations for several languages</li>
        <li>Various small code improvements and fixes</li>
        <li>Update contact information for user support</li>
        <li>Set default map to OSM instead of an empty map</li>
        <li>Allow the app to run if screen is off</li>
    </update>
    <update name="2020.03.08" id="20200308" time="05.03.2020">
        <li>Fixed broken download of cartridges from wherigo.com by switching to https</li>                   
        <li>Change the permissions handling to fulfill the requirements for Google Play</li>
        <li>Update the code to support Android targetSdk 28</li>
        <li>Removed and updated map online providers, fixed non working online maps</li>
        <li>Improved German, Slovak translations</li>
        <li>Minor GUI and code improvements</li>
    </update>
    <update name="0.9.3" id="44" time="14.7.2017">
        <li>Added support for animated GIF and MP4.</li>
        <li>Added Norwegian, Catalan languages</li>
        <li>Improved German, Japanese languages</li>
        <li>Clickable URLs in descriptions</li>
        <li>Task state fixed, icons improved</li>
        <li>Fixed occasional crashing when using timer or when the app is closing</li>
        <li>Improved error messages when downloading a cartridge</li>
        <li>Fixed issue with compass and timer</li>
    </update>
</document>
